class EnglishQuestions():
            level_1 = [
                    {"question":"Test A: We ___ American.",
                    "answers":"a not b not are c aren’t d isn’t",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"___ this magazine before?",
                    "answers":"a Do you read b Are you going to read c Are you reading d Have you read",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"This is our new teacher. ___ name is Mark.",
                    "answers":"a His b Her c Its d He",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"He ___ the newspaper every day.",
                    "answers":"a read b reads c doesn’t reads d don’t reads",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"Is Mont Blanc ___ mountain in Europe?",
                    "answers":"a the higher b the most highest c the more high d the highest",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"British people ___ tea with milk.",
                    "answers":"a to drink b drink c drinks d are drink",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"___ you like Chinese food?",
                    "answers":"a Do b Does c Are d Is",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"It’s my ___ computer.",
                    "answers":"a parents b parents’ c parent d parent’s",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"Could we ___ the bill, please?",
                    "answers":"a take b want c have d ask",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"The people ___ in room 12.",
                    "answers":"a is b am c are d be",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"It’s ten ___ seven.",
                    "answers":"a to b for c at d in",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I ___ to classical music.",
                    "answers":"a never to listen b listen never c never listen d don’t never listen",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"Would you like ___ coffee?",
                    "answers":"a other b another c some other d more one",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"I haven’t ___ this photo before.",
                    "answers":"a see b saw c to see d seen",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"I can’t see. Where are my ___?",
                    "answers":"a glasses b stamps c keys d lipsticks",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I like ___ in the morning.",
                    "answers":"a that I work b working c work d to be work",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"Thanks for ___.",
                    "answers":"a all b the all c everything d all things",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"‘Was Debussy from France?’ ‘Yes, ___.’",
                    "answers":"a he were b was c there were d he was",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"I’m Italian. ___ family are from Venice.",
                    "answers":"a Our b My c Her d Me",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"What ___ do tomorrow?",
                    "answers":"a are you going b you going c are you going to d do you go to",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"Can I pay ___ credit card?",
                    "answers":"a by b in c on d with",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"This isn’t my money. It’s ___.",
                    "answers":"a to you b the yours c your d yours",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"Tonight’s dinner is ___ than last night’s.",
                    "answers":"a more good b gooder c better d more better",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"They didn’t ___ the tickets.",
                    "answers":"a booking b booked c to book d book",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"They’re ___.",
                    "answers":"a bigs cars b cars bigs c big cars d bigs car",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"___ the time?",
                    "answers":"a What’s b What is it c What d What it is",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"She ___ to the gym every day.",
                    "answers":"a gets b goes c has d does",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"I ___ do my homework last night.",
                    "answers":"a not could b didn’t can c couldn’t d can’t",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"There ___ telephone in my hotel room.",
                    "answers":"a wasn’t a b weren’t a c weren’t any d wasn’t some",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"He ___ playing the piano.",
                    "answers":"a are b does c is d has",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"He ___ jeans.",
                    "answers":"a doesn’t usually wear b isn’t usually wearing c wears usually d doesn’t wear usually",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I ___ my new job last week.",
                    "answers":"a have begun b began c am begin d begin",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"There isn’t ___ pasta in the kitchen.",
                    "answers":"a some b many c a d any",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"She ___ to cook for her boyfriend.",
                    "answers":"a isn’t going b isn’t go c aren’t going d doesn’t go",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"The elephant is ___ land animal in the world.",
                    "answers":"a the bigger b the most big c biggest d the biggest",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"___ yesterday?",
                    "answers":"a You studied b Did you studied c Did you study d Studied you",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"James would like ___ basketball.",
                    "answers":"a playing b to play c play d to playing",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"I always ___.",
                    "answers":"a work hard b hard work c hardly work d work hardly",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"We ___ to Canada.",
                    "answers":"a haven’t be b hasn’t been c hasn’t be d haven’t been",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"He ___ follow instructions.",
                    "answers":"a doesn’t can b not can c isn’t can d can’t", 
                    "right_answer":"d"}
                    ]

            level_2 = [
                    {"question":"It ___ when they went out.", 
                    "answers":"a rained b was raining c is raining d was to rain",
                    "right_answer":"b"}, 
                    {"question":"Did you ___ TV last night?", 
                    "answers":"a watch b see c look at d listen",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"That’s the hotel ___ we had lunch.", 
                    "answers":"a what b where c that d which",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"Diana ___ some wine when she went to France.", 
                    "answers":"a bought b buyed c boot d did buy",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I don’t get ___ very well with my brother.", 
                    "answers":"a by b from c on d to",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"Tom always ___ golf on Sundays.", 
                    "answers":"a plays b play c to play d is plays",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"Mary ___ a key when she was cleaning her car.", 
                    "answers":"a was finding b finded c founded d found",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"___ I worked hard, I didn’t pass the test.", 
                    "answers":"a Although b So c Because d But",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"My parents ___ to stay with us next week.", 
                    "answers":"a comes b coming c is coming d are coming",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"Come on, it’s time ___.", 
                    "answers":"a to go b going c we go d go",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"Can you look ___ my dog this weekend?", 
                    "answers":"a with b away c up d after",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"Who ___ the answer to this question?", 
                    "answers":"a knows b know c does know d does knows",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"When I got to work I remembered that ___ my mobile at home.", 
                    "answers":"a I’d leave b I was leaving c I’d left d I left",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"My father ___ be a builder.", 
                    "answers":"a used to b was c use to d did use to",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I haven’t tidied my office ___.", 
                    "answers":"a just b already c yet d since",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"I can sing, but not as ___ as my sister.", 
                    "answers":"a well b good c best d better",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"That’s my money! Give ___!", 
                    "answers":"a back b it back c back it d it",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"Richard isn’t very good ___.", 
                    "answers":"a to dance b at dancing c dancing d dance",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"I’m sure Canada isn’t as big ___ Russia.", 
                    "answers":"a as b than c to d like",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"It’s important ___ too much alcohol.", 
                    "answers":"a not to drinking b not to drink c not drink d not drinks",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"We ___ take a map.", 
                    "answers":"a should b should to c might to d might",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"___ dinner in a restaurant today.", 
                    "answers":"a I have b I having c I’m having d I’m to have",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"Cameras aren’t allowed here – you ___ take photos.", 
                    "answers":"a mustn’t b don’t have to c must not to d have to",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"Pam ___ eat cheese, but she does now.", 
                    "answers":"a didn’t used to b did use to c didn’t use to d wasn’t to",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"We ___ late and the game had already started.", 
                    "answers":"a arrived b had arrived c didn’t arrive d were arriving",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"Your diet is terrible. You don’t eat ___.", 
                    "answers":"a many vegetables b enough vegetable c vegetables enough d many vegetable",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"If we had the money, we ___ get a taxi.", 
                    "answers":"a will can b can c would can d could",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"___ my best friend since 1999.", 
                    "answers":"a I’ve known b I knew c I’m knowing d I know",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"You ___ the new café in town. The coffee’s terrible.", 
                    "answers":"a aren’t like b won’t like c isn’t like d won’t liking",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"There’s always a lot of traffic going ___ the bridge.", 
                    "answers":"a over b in c at d through",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"This road was built ___ the Romans.", 
                    "answers":"a of b for c by d with",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"Michelangelo ___ some of his best works in Rome.", 
                    "answers":"a painted b was painted c is painting d has painted",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"You eat ___ chocolate – you really should give up.", 
                    "answers":"a too much b enough c very many d much",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"How ___ your name?", 
                    "answers":"a is it pronounced b you pronounce c do you pronounce d to pronounce",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"I ___ come to the party tonight.", 
                    "answers":"a might not b don’t might c don’t to d not",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I’m really tired – I only got ___ hours’ sleep.", 
                    "answers":"a not many b a few c a little d few",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"Your papers are on the floor. Why don’t you ___?", 
                    "answers":"a pick them up b pick up them c pick up to them d pick them",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"If you take your time, ___ the right decision.", 
                    "answers":"a you make b you’d make c you’ll make d you’re making",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"I ___ the museum because I hadn’t brought a map.", 
                    "answers":"a couldn’t find b couldn’t to find c can’t find d hadn’t found",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"She told me ___ number, but I can’t remember it.", 
                    "answers":"a my b his c her d hers",
                    "right_answer":"c"}               
                    ]
            level_3 = [
                    {"question":"___ Kate nor I want to go to London.", 
                    "answers":"a Neither b Both c Either d Not",
                    "right_answer":"a"}, 
                    {"question":"We ___ together since last year.",
                    "answers":"a live b are living c lived d ’ve been living",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"What’s the matter? You ___ sad.", 
                    "answers":"a see b look like c look d ’re look",
                    "right_answer":"c"}, 
                    {"question":"This food isn’t ___.",
                    "answers":"a enough hot b hot enough c much hot d very much hot",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"What ___ tomorrow night?", 
                    "answers":"a are you doing b do you do c you do d are you do",
                    "right_answer":"a"}, 
                    {"question":"There were ___ people at the match.",
                    "answers":"a very little b very small c very few d not much",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"They won’t ___ use their mobiles.", 
                    "answers":"a can b be able c be able to d can to",
                    "right_answer":"c"}, 
                    {"question":"When is it going to stop ___?",
                    "answers":"a to rain b rain c to raining d raining",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"We enjoyed ___ at the party.", 
                    "answers":"a each b each other c ourselves d us",
                    "right_answer":"c"}, 
                    {"question":"His parents didn’t ___ him go out.",
                    "answers":"a allow b let c permit d leave",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"We were really ___ with the weather.", 
                    "answers":"a disappointed b disappoint c disappointing d disappointment",
                    "right_answer":"a"}, 
                    {"question":"She doesn’t go to the gym ___.",
                    "answers":"a no more b no longer c more d any more",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"I studied chemistry at ___ university.", 
                    "answers":"a the b – c a d an",
                    "right_answer":"b"}, 
                    {"question":"That’s the house ___ we live.",
                    "answers":"a – b which c that d where",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"I have a bath ___ I get home.", 
                    "answers":"a as soon as b as soon c so soon that d when that",
                    "right_answer":"a"}, 
                    {"question":"Would you marry him if he ___ you?",
                    "answers":"a would ask b asks c did ask d asked",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"I can’t ___ to buy a new car.", 
                    "answers":"a afford b spend c pay d think",
                    "right_answer":"a"}, 
                    {"question":"They’ll move to France when their baby ___.",
                    "answers":"a will be born b is being born c is born d would be born",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"She speaks English ___ than me.", 
                    "answers":"a more better b better c more well d so better",
                    "right_answer":"b"}, 
                    {"question":"Can I ___ cheque?",
                    "answers":"a pay by b pay with c pay in d pay on",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I don’t like ___ coffee or tea.", 
                    "answers":"a neither b or c both d either",
                    "right_answer":"d"}, 
                    {"question":"I ___ get in through the window.",
                    "answers":"a managed to b could to c was able d managed",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"I’m tired. I ___ all day.", 
                    "answers":"a study b ’ve been studying c ’m studying d was studying",
                    "right_answer":"b"}, 
                    {"question":"I ___ go to the dentist yesterday.",
                    "answers":"a must b musted c had to d have to",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                     {"question":"That’s the boy ___ parents I met.",
                    "answers":"a which b whom c who d whose",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"When is that letter ___?",
                    "answers":"a going to be sent b going to send c will be sent d to send",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                     {"question":"Is there a tennis ___ near here?",
                    "answers":"a pitch b place c stadium d court",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                    {"question":"I refused ___ to them.",
                    "answers":"a to talk b talk c to talking d talking",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                     {"question":"Can you tell me where ___?",
                    "answers":"a the post office is b is the post office c the post office d post office",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"He needs to ___ a diet.",
                    "answers":"a do b get c go on d be",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                     {"question":"He said he ___ school in 1998.",
                    "answers":"a left b leaves c has left d leave",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    {"question":"He works too hard so it’s not ___ he’s ill.",
                    "answers":"a surprise b to surprise c surprising d surprised",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                     {"question":"I think the battery’s ___ in this camera.",
                    "answers":"a out b missing c losing d missed",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                    {"question":"He didn’t buy that computer, ___?",
                    "answers":"a is it b didn’t he c did he d isn’t it",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                     {"question":"Can you ___ a favour?",
                    "answers":"a make b make me c do d do me",
                    "right_answer":"d"},
                     {"question":"They don’t get ___ very well.",
                    "answers":"a together b on c in d by",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                     {"question":"Do you ___ if I open the window?",
                    "answers":"a matter b mind c think d wish",
                    "right_answer":"b"},
                     {"question":"Tell him ___.",
                    "answers":"a not to come b not come c not coming d don’t come",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                     {"question":"I’ll take some water ___ I get thirsty.",
                    "answers":"a so b although c in case d unless",
                    "right_answer":"c"},
                    {"question":"I never ___ eat so much.",
                    "answers":"a used to b didn’t used to c use to d didn’t use to",
                    "right_answer":"a"},
                    ]      
